{
    "subject": "Umaru_Yar'Adua",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Turai_Yar'Adua",
    "human_readable": "Umaru Yar'Adua is married to Turai Yar'Adua.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9807776808738708,
            "question": "Who is married to Umaru Yar'Adua?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9790061116218567,
            "question": "Is Umaru Yar'Adua married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9773543477058411,
            "question": "To whom was Umaru Yar'Adua married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9734364151954651,
            "question": "Name the wife of Umaru Yar'Adua."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9403322339057922,
            "question": "Is Turai Yar'Adua related to Umaru Yar'Adua?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9237097501754761,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Umaru Yar'Adua and Turai Yar'Adua?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9165188074111938,
            "question": "What is the name of Umaru Yar'Adua's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9160650968551636,
            "question": "Umaru Yar'Adua's spouse's name is?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9087303280830383,
            "question": "What is the name of Umaru Yar'Adua's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8386009335517883,
            "question": "Who is Turai Yar'Adua?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Umaru Yar'Adua is married to Turai Yar'Adua.",
            "html": "yago_9259_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Umaru Yar'Adua's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_9259_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Umaru Yar'Adua's spouse's name is?",
            "html": "yago_9259_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Umaru Yar'Adua's wife?",
            "html": "yago_9259_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9259_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9259_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9259_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9259_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9259_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9259_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9259_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9259_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9259_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9259_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I can confirm that the triple \"Umaru Yar'Adua is married to Turai Yar'Adua\" is supported by the documents.\n\nHere's the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe multiple mentions of Umaru Yar'Adua marrying Turai Umaru Yar'Adua in different documents confirm that they are indeed married."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Umaru Musa Yar'Adua was married to Turai Yar'Adua, with details such as the year of their marriage (1975) and the number of children they had."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}